

Gabriel Dell'Aiuto (1996)

Italian—Dominican Designer, Product Developer, ex CERN Design Intern, Graduating in Law at the University of Bologna; alumni, University of California, Santa Cruz.

In my studies I focus on cognitive theories, design thinking methods and applied research. I have experiences the fashion and design industry, in-house and as a sole practictioner.

Experience

Teddy Fresh Inc Accessories Designer & Product Developer April 2022 – October 2022 Los Angeles, California, US (remote)

GCDS Graphic Designer, Accessories Designer, Fashion Designer June 2021 – March 2022 Milan, Italy

CERN Ideasquare Liasion Company: YOOX Net-A-Porter Group Design Intern October 2019 — February 2020 Bologna, Italy / Geneve, Switzerland

Solo Practice
Accessory Designer,
Graphic Designer,
Digital Product Designer,
Project Manager,
Advertisement.
2020 – present

Education

Alma Mater Studiorum, University of Bologna Law (Juris Doctor, JD) 2015 — early 2023 GPA: 3.8 Bologna, Italy

University of California, Santa Cruz Visiting Student, 2018 – 2019 Philosophy of Cognitive Sciences GPA: 3.9 Santa Cruz, California, US

Scuola di Politiche, Agenzia di Ricerca e Legislazione Annual Course 2016 – 2017 Rome, Italy

Softwares & Extra

Adobe, Rhino, Grasshopper, Zbrush, Blender, Substance, Marvelous Designer, Clo3D, Unity.

Developer Tools: Github, HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, C#, Python, 3D Printing.

Nationality: Italian, Dominican Languages: English, Italian, Spanish

Contacts

(IT): +39 3464927346 dellaiutogabriel@gmail.com https://grayz.app